Om
again to the ICICI Lamba Brokers
Premier League two and two six season three one more
match one more exciting contest
Howden vs El Alla Strikers in the
center Alliance strike one the tock did to
bowl first and that's a good strike
will the fielder will stop no the ball will go
for four runs
good strike from Vishal Jadhav
that's a clean hit and into the mid wicket
region for four runs four balls seven runs
no wicket team howden
just a single run
om
so one gone 12 team howden
change in the field settings from the team
Alliance Strikers
this game of five overs
both the teams have won this match.  Winning the first match.
Winner vs Winner
and Experience Content Satyendra Singh
That's a good bowling He
made the batsman dancing on the pitch
looking for a big one but beaten completely
Vishal Jadhav
is a single taken
Oh wow That's an excellent shot high in the
air
Excellent effort by the fielder that will go all the way
for six runs
Vishal hit Vishal hit an excellent shot
Good timing Reminds me of the batting of Adam
Gilchrist The way he played
in that era Very
good to watch All Adam Gilchrist
fans will relate
1.4 24 No Loss Team Hown
Excellent timing We are talking about only
in
Satyendra Singh but this time he went
expensive 13 runs conceded
to 25 for No Loss Team Hown
It's time for the Alliance Strikers
fielding side to make a  Comeback in this match they
will restrict something on the board two
overs 25 runs no wickets that's
under Deepa need four fielders inside
a circle shot fine leg
shot mid wicket we are shot third man and shot
extra cover that four fielders inside
circle standing
a bet of fumble and capitalise to run.  They are
going for three runs.
Three runs taken.
Excellent cricket.  Good observation by
both the batters.  A good communication.  That's the key they
give two plus one run in the over throw
om
that's hit hard will get only a
single run good throw
direct throw they are
looking for the wicket here team alliance
strikers
to need a lot
needed a break through needed now Ashish
and Vishal looking good touch the left right
combination
only a single both
the batsmen rotating the strike.  It
looks like they will play till the end of the
first innings.
2.432 for no loss.
2.5
33 A very good stop and the follow through and that's the end of
the over.
Seven runs conceded from Kaushik.
33 runs after three overs. No wicket. Team Howden.
Satyendra Singh once again expensive in his
first over. 13 runs conceded and now the team
needs a break through. The
fielder is standing at mid-wicket. They are
going for two runs. The throw is very good but
that distance
makes it not easy to throw directly on to the
wicketkeeper and directly on to
the stumps. On the pitch, two runs are taken. 36 on the board after
3.2
Good batting by Ashish 14 of 14 to force
Vishal 20 of 11 with one four and one six.
Something new innovation. Tried toster
delivery to play that scoop shot but there is a
fielder standing at short fine leg. Will
get only a single.
Left to right combination.
Vishal and Ashish
only got the outside edge. Very good stop.
Fielder going for two.  Runs the throw at the non-
striker and but two runs again good running
39 fun loss wow
once again aerial route and six runs
absolutely fantastic hit from Vishal we have seen
this season two also previous year
and now also absolutely fantastic
destructive batsman second six from bat
same region
batting 28 of 13 one four and two sixes
wow
last ball coming up expensive Satyan Singh
25 runs in 1.5
45 on the board still one over to go after this
ball
looking for a big one not got the connection
this time will take strike for the next
over
so four o gone 46 for no loss team once again
looking to play for a big one they
going for two but
non-striker batsman
said no for run
Aniket Kerkar the new batsman at number three after getting
retired out
last five balls of the
first innings
om
wow excellent shot jagah bana khel diya ch  The
ball has been sent straight to the turf
for practice
with this how done 50 runs completed
50 for the team how done
4.4 53 for one last two balls coming up
three sixes in this innings one from
Aniket and two from Vishal three
sixes and three forces
only a single run chance for the run out but
batsman they are very quick
last ball coming up 54 for one
will Vishal hit one more big Vishal will hit
for six runs bat it really well 30
and 16 one four and two maximum hits
this time get connection to played shot one leg bye will be
the signal yes so five was gone
55 for one
and is that one ball left they
one ball left that is
clean bowled timber
shattered and dream dream shattered
so last ball wicket
so 55 and the target will be 56 to chase stay
tuned to watch ICI Lum Brokers
Premier League two to six season three
the Mumbai edition ok may
I request the team how done team
please  As soon as possible
Set up the field fast and alliance
strikers The two batters Come as soon as possible
If you come early In the count of
three to one Nobody comes to my side Ice cream
party.
3 to 1
Anirudh ji said I have come.
Only Anuruddha ji is going to get the party.
Okay welcome back once again ICI Brokers
Premier League Two and 26
Mumbai Edition Season Three everyone is welcome
and once again
joining in the com box with me, the expert in Sher's
poet Mr. Tos Naushad Khan ji
welcome you
medicine, poison,
jam, what all?
I have come.  Tell me what are the arrangements?
What is the matter.  What is the matter.
Everything is arranged.  There is arrangement for food here.
First aid box is available.
Entertainment is arranged and it remains to be seen
who will win this match.  It is important.   It
is a big target for 56. Naushad ji, it may be a
bit difficult to hit 56 in five overs.
This can be possible if we use the power play well.  Let's see
how he bats now.
Om, the
first ball, the
batsman steps out and goes to hit it to mid-off [music].
But it edges and he drops an easy catch at cover.
Catching a catch is very important to win a match
and a simple catch can be dropped.   Of
course they say catches vs matches.
The catch was missed, the dream was shattered.
And went on the back foot and pulled.  Very nice
shot.   Yes,
for four runs, there was a
slight misjudgement by the fielder from his side here, if he had stopped it here then the
runs would not have been scored here, but with back to back
runs coming here, he
wanted to pull six runs and not take a wicket.  Took the inside edge of the bat
and one run.
Left-handed strike pay.   Let's
see how he bowls now.
Taking the fourth ball of this over, the bowler gave a
very good shot and equally good
fielding.
Eight runs in four balls. A
very good square cut ball is going
outside the boundary line for four runs. It was a
short shot of a plain ball and he went on the back foot and did a
good square cut. A
very good and excellent stroke of cricket, he
sent the ball back to where it was.   Yes, he is
batting very well.  Five
balls, 12 runs, no wickets.
Again he went forward and tried to push it to mid off.  The
ball took the outside edge and the
wicketkeeper took a very good catch.
12 runs in one over.
One wicket.   He wanted to come
forward and kill me.  That's why it is said that she
calls but I don't want to go.
This is the world, not the place to go.  My son, fall in
love with someone.
But love is not about crossing the limits.
What is the matter.  What is the matter.
Very good call drive
excellent shot the ball is going for four runs
very good sound from the bat the ball went
out of the ground
wanted to square cut the next ball.   The
ball took an edge and went to third man.
One over, two balls,
17 runs and one wicket.   You are doing
very well.  Now it remains to be seen whether he can
complete this run or not.   He wanted to
come forward and hit the next ball again.   The
ball took the outside edge and the wicketkeeper did
his job.  One run.
Another three ball 18 runs one wicket
was a full toss ball.  He has played it towards mid-wicket.
Low full toss for two runs.
Nice pick.
Team score 20 runs.   The
shot is pulled.  The fielder is
under the ball and a very good catch.
One over, five balls, 20 runs, two wickets.
Fielder Name Please Catch Taken By
Thank You Very Much Parth
So here you have performed brilliantly today
Mr Om Sir
what would you like to say to Nausha ji for umpiring in the com box?
Om Sir looks innocent.  He is very clever at heart.   The
world says that the crazy person is great.  He himself
is 30 years old and the bride is 60 years old.
Standing in the shadow of a falling wall.
Should there be [laughter]
applause?  Let there be applause.
Wow, very interesting.
So is it true what you said?
We old people are very important in your gatherings.  If
we are not there then who will
tie the turban?
To has gone 24 to
36 from 18 balls.   The
umpire needs to speed up a bit here.
Because we have a little time.  We are back
in time
and this time it's a good strike, there is a
fielder standing in the deep, running in and the throw was not
that fine, the batsman took
two runs here, running fast
between the wickets, Prasad and Satyendra
Singh, now both the batsmen have a big
responsibility.  33 runs needed in 16 balls.
Toast delivery and play will they go for two once again no this
time good throw direct
throw at the non-striker and just a
single
24 for two this
time is not got the proper elevation to
play that big hit there was a
toast delivery
only a single
both the batsmen are rotating the strike here
now those two big hits
can change the match completely and two wickets back to
back team Howden will try here
will wait for the umpire signal
that's leg bye so very
good over from Vishal Jadhav just
considered five runs
something to chase for Vishal Jadhav they are
defending very well but oh that
went for a dot ball good bowling but let's see now if they can get the
momentum to
pressure more they need 30 runs in two overs and that's the
pressure from the team how end to
alliance strikers 30 runs in 12 balls 15
runs every over not easy to chase so either
15 runs  20 runs needed from the batting
team to get this target chased at least closer
30 runs and 12 balls
the crucial over of the match
going backfoot and
striking really well for a single so good
field heads up from captain Vishal one
fielder deep backward square leg one at mid
wicket one at deep cover long off long
on just
a single good bowling good fielding
28 runs needed in 10 balls remains to be seen
who will be in charge here all the
strikers or how done
Prasad will take strike
fours going outside the off side line for a wide would
like to keep it a little away Siddhant is trying to
skip it away from the batsman's arc
and this time played for a single headed long off
o bit of misfield there
and all the way for four runs
misfield by the skipper Vishal at long off
and the ball went for four runs
with this four runs now 23 runs needed in nine balls.
23 from no balls.
Going on the back foot
playing at long on going for two runs
and excellent running between the wickets
good batting by Prasad and Sathyan
21 runs in eight balls eight balls and 21 to get need that one
big hit at least that's
high in the air catches win matches
well taken there at the fielder standing at
mid wicket that's a one more wicket fall and
yes we can say the team has done almost 70%
in the match winning mode
3.5 35 for three in seven balls 21 runs
every ball three runs every ball boundary
very tough now for the team alliance
strikers
sanjay the new batter
o that's a very good bowling
conceded nine runs
so four has gone 35 for three and 21 runs, 21
runs in six balls.
Excellent bowling, good over.
That one over from Vishal Jadhav five runs
complete change
the course of the match
and Ashish one 8 for one Siddh two 21 for two that's
high in the air
and taken and gone one more
wicket falls much needed break through
and good catch taken by Aniket Long on
still the team try their level best to chase this
target of 56
needed in five balls 21 runs
20 four balls they will
go for two
and they will get two runs.
Three balls 18 runs.
Three big hits.   It
is difficult.  It is very difficult.  Three balls
18 runs.
Now this is the match of team Howden
a good bowling performance in
defending the total now let's see by how many
margin they will win this match good
stop by Ashish Kundu
that is in the end
catches taken was the match
team Howden has done the fantastic job.   Are
?